Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Music Ehama
難しいスページ 乾くほど願い
水が糸を伝え 誰かにかなら困難な数
Fuck you.
The cue is filled with influences, it certainly has to be placed in easy ways for everyone watching.
In the middle of the day, we're going to be in the middle of the night
We're going to open the door now
Let's finish
Man, it's huge!
We can't even hope to defeat something that big
For now, we need to get the children out of here
Go! Get on his back and he'll take you to safety
Amazing!
Wow, it's so warm
It could take half an hour or more for us to get them all out
We'll have to hold our ground until then
I'm not letting you get any closer
Die
All of you
You aren't yourself anymore
What did she do to you?
Do you know me? I'm your brother!
Why would you save me?
You can't die! Take responsibility for what you did
That's the punishment you deserve
Plus your own brother just tried to kill you and that's not cool!
He's even sicker than I thought he would!
My sword seems to work fine on you so I'll just cut you down to size!
Your anti-magic is the cutest but even it won't take him down that easy
You saw that dark magic tool
It drains the life force from the subject and makes them swell and swell with magic power!
She's a special kind of crazy
It just grows right back!
I've got a little present for you, Asta!
Here!
Sister!
Aw! You interrupted us again!
That's starting to get annoying!
I don't have time for crusty old ladies and their feeble magic power!
You'd better watch your tone with me, little whippersnapper!
It's true that our bodies produce less magic power as we age
But no matter how old you are, you can always increase your ability to work with natural mana
When it comes to technique, I'm a master
Your youth has nothing on my experience
Try me! You'll see what I can do!
Geez, you're loud!
You should try not to get so worked up
You'll keel over and die if you're not more careful
I'm not going to lose to a mouthy brat!
I'm doing my best
But I can't fight as well as I'd like to while covering the children's escape
This is going to go downhill fast
Damn Ghosh, running away like a selfish idiot he's always been
We have to help them, brother!
No, I'm taking you back to the village
Please, it's not too late! Turn around!
My magic is useless against that woman
And now with that mud monster she's got backing her up, it would be an even riskier fight
I'm not going to put you in that kind of danger
What about the others?
As long as you're safe, I don't give a damn about them
That's right, no one else matters
What else matters?
The renowned house Adlai
They're the envy of all other noble families
Little Ghosh is so intelligent
Just like his father
And Marie takes after her mother
Look how beautiful she is
Do you have a moment to talk business?
I believe he said something about wanting to invest
What?
Mother and father can't be dead, that's impossible
It's true, I'm afraid
They were attacked by bandits on their way home from my office
You won't have to worry about any of the pesky financial details though
Since they left everything they had to me
And he does mean everything
You're lying
It was you who
That's enough
That look, such insolence
Who could love a brat like that?
Get out of my house
You'll be okay Marie, I'm here
I promise I'll protect you
No matter what it takes
That's what I said
You again?
Get back here
I'll steal anything for Marie
Is it good?
That's all I need
To see Marie smile
Give me all your money
Careful, I'm a noble you know
As a noble isn't it your duty to help people in need like me?
Only Marie matters
Stop right there
Stop right there!
We're arresting you for crimes against the kingdom
Go right ahead, I'd like to see you try
Please, you insolent street rat
Marie
I've never cared about anyone else and I won't start now
doin'
J winner made us most uncool-bank brother ever, I hate you!
I've never cared about anyone else, and I won't start now.
You've made us most uncle big brother ever! I hate you!
I know it hasn't been easy.
And there have been people who have done really awful things to us.
But Sister Teresa and the church kids are different.
The only reason I don't get lonely when you're gone is because I've got them.
They're my friends!
Isn't that why you joined the Magic Knights? So you wouldn't be alone?
People's lives are all connected, you know?
Everybody has to have friends. They're what make us who we are!
Don't you see?
Besides, Magic Knights are supposed to keep people safe, right?
I was so proud when I found that you were going to become a Magic Knight.
And I want to keep being proud of you. Please, brother.
Marie.
Hey! Over here!
It's Marco!
I was worried about you. I'm glad you're okay.
I was real scared, but then Sister and Asta showed up.
I knew they would come to rescue us!
Hey, kid, where'd you get that robe you're wearing?
It's Asta's. He let me borrow it.
I was afraid of being alone while he and Sister came here to save the other kids.
But he told me it's full of Magic Knight courage!
I'm sure I'll be safe enough if I wait out here with Marco.
You go back and help the others.
Don't worry! I won't let anything bad happen to Marie!
You better not, you sad excuse for a bodyguard, or something equally bad will happen to you, I promise.
Brother!
Marco!
Marie!
You're here!
I'm glad you're okay.
Sister got us out using her awesome flame magic!
She and Asta are still back there fighting, but the monster's really strong!
It's fine, you'll see. My big brother's gonna go and help them.
He and Asta are in the same Magic Knight Squad, so they have to stick together.
Wow!
The same as Asta?
Then he must be super strong!
Yeah!
Marie, you better keep yourself well hidden.
Right.
Big Brother!
Good luck!
Asta this, Asta that...
What's so great about him anyway?
The captain, the other squad members, they're all crazy about this kid.
But he was basically useless back there.
He and the old hag have probably given up and made a run for it by now.
When you get down to it, people will always put themselves ahead of others.
That's just the way the world works.
No. Not yet.
I'm not done!
You don't know when to quit, huh?
Just forget about protecting them and let me capture you already.
We'll have so much fun!
Forget about protecting them?
No way!
Never!
Not a chance!
You would have to kill me first!
Which isn't gonna happen!
Because there's no way I'm gonna die before I become a wizard king!
Quick Asa!
On your right!
You know, for someone who is going on and on about not dying today, it sure did look like you were about to.
Ghost, you came back! Why'd you run away in the first place, you jerk!?
No way!
Never!
Not a chance!
No way!
What?
Never!
No way!
It's not like that!
For someone who is going on and on about not dying today, it sure did look like you were about
to!
Ghost, you came back!
Why'd you run away in the first place, you jerk?!
I wasn't running away. I just needed to get Marie to safety.
So the idiot decided to come back and help after all.
I'll take you on myself.
No, you can't!
Been there, tried that! It didn't work!
I'll fight the best that I can, so Marie will love me.
And then she'll be proud of her big brother again!
Go real double!
Double refrain!
Oh man, that's so cool!
Anytime we cut part of it off, more magic pours in and repairs the damage.
Pretty frustrating, huh?
I haven't even scratched that woman.
This is my worst pairing since the captain.
Should I play my trump card? No.
No matter how strong my mirror magic becomes, it won't work.
Ghost, are you okay?
Damn. This isn't how I wanted to die.
Why'd you go after it alone like that? We're supposed to be in this together!
We're squad mates and friends, aren't we?
And that means when we fight, I protect you and you protect me!
Then nobody can take either of us down!
That's what I call a foolproof strategy!
That's what I call a sloppy strategy.
He really is an idiot.
Although, I knew someone else who fought sloppy.
So you still want to fight?
Cause I can tell you right now, you're done running.
But my sister, she's waiting.
Oh really?
Well, if she's that important to you, come and join my squad.
Pay's pretty decent.
You want me to join a magic knight squad?
But I'm an escaped criminal.
And?
And I don't trust people!
And I'm a thief!
And the only thing I care about is my sister!
Fine.
I won't stop you.
Protect whatever you think needs protecting.
Keep doing that and it'll help someone someday.
Captain.
Did you know this would happen eventually?
Hey sister, how's the escape plan going?
Not many left now.
I have no choice.
I don't get why, but Marie would be heartbroken if you died.
So I'll protect you.
Is this boy really Ghosh?
Don't act like you're doing me a favor here!
We're friends!
Helping each other is what we do!
Hey, watch the attitude.
As your senior squad member, I will be treated with respect.
Hold on. What's happening?
Not sure.
It's...
Like that time in the dungeon.
Yeah!
Huh?
Ah! That doesn't hurt it either!
Cool! What was that?
Some kind of flying anti-magic slash thing?
How did you do it? Tell me! Tell me!
If we're going to defeat this thing,
we need to hit it hard all at once faster than it can regenerate.
Our best bet would probably be Asta's slash attack.
But even that doesn't hit fast enough.
What if I use my magic on someone else?
Gauche, who had spent his life distrusting others
and always preferred to work alone,
had never before imagined using his magic to support somebody else.
But from his desperation to win back Marie's love,
his grudging acceptance of Asta came forth.
A fundamentally similar yet entirely different spell
inscribed on a new page in his grimoire.
And not a moment too soon.
Good. But I don't have enough magic power to cast this.
Hey, old hag.
Buy me some time to renew my mana.
Please.
You cad, ordering an old lady around like that.
I won't be able to hold out for very long, so make it snappy!
You've used up all the good stuff, and what's left just isn't going to cut it.
It's your turn to play, Asta.
Do your slash thing again.
Yeah, trust me.
I would if I could.
Ah, pretty pooper.
I've kept it hidden, but using it now may be our only way out of this.
Asta!
What's up?
Look at me.
My left eye has been replaced with a mirror magic tool.
I'll use the power stored inside to cast my new spell.
Mirror magic!
Marage Brigade!
Go!
Not yet!
I'm not dead!
We did it!
Incredible.
They combined their magics?
Whatever they did, it looks like they were finally able to drain the power out of that
creature.
Goodbye, brother.
Jeez, you're such a crybaby.
How much longer are you going to keep up the waterworks?
Here, I guess you can have this.
Thanks, brother Baro!
I swear, I'll hate her forever for turning you into that monster.
And me, how can I forgive myself for blindly following you and doing whatever you ordered
me to do, no matter how awful it was?
What you said before was right.
I have to take responsibility for the things I've done.
I'll do it.
I will atone for my sins and for my brothers, too.
Good.
And once you get that out of the way, you and I should be friends.
With all the cool magic you can do, I bet you're going to be a pretty popular guy.
Huh?
That would be…
It's that bright light again.
So much magic power.
I've never felt anything this huge before.
I didn't see anything.
What happened?
Another one?
Haven't they done enough damage already?
Asha!
No, old hag!
Sister!
You have injured my compatriot.
It's only fair that I return the favor.
It's him!
The guy we saw at the group's hideout!
I haven't introduced myself yet, have I?
I am the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Call me Licht.
No…
No way…
Just like Yunus…
A four-leaf clover grimoire!
What do you mean we've got here?
Yes, I have a light bulb.
Money is not there.
With us.
Just like Yunus…
Interesting to him.
Who contacted me?
Like Danianya.
es
me
Oh, no, no.
No, no, no.
mommy
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Blulls in the impossible
You don't will give me to your dreams
Love After the dream
Fly!
Clover Clips!
Marie's in danger.
And a one, two, three!
How to say no to an angel?
As much as I like to spoil Marie,
I must sometimes harden my heart
and decline her requests no matter how
angelically she makes them.
Like so.
Hey, Big Brother, please go back to help Sister and Asta.
No, you'd be in danger if I did.
Hey, Big Brother, I want some rice gratin with hot, melty cheese.
No, your tongue would be in danger.
It would get burned.
Hey, Big Brother, can we stay out here in the sun all day?
No!
Your skin would be in danger if you stay out in full sun too long.
UV rays are a mighty foe.
Hey, Big Brother, show me a super cool spell.
No!
Wait, yes.
Marie, look at me.
Mirage Brigade!
Big Brother, you're awesome!
Uh-oh.
Now I'm in danger.
Ugh.
Baby Brother?
This guy was in the eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout.
You attack the Clover Kingdom and Captain Foigolion!
You won't get away with it!
Black Clover, page 34.
Light magic versus dark magic.
Whoa!
Captain Yami!
Granny Brisco Bros.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh determine!
Sorry!
龍hetti.
You won't have to worry.
voluntary tour realm!
Honey!
You won't have to worry!
You won't have enough years, you won't have to worry!
I'm returned!
Okay, 중요 chaque.
Let's see if we have attacked!